https://bogglesworldesl.com/privacy.htm

Throughout
the site we collect information of a non-personally identifiable
nature such as I.P. address and browser. We maintain aggregate collections
of this information.
We do
collect personally identifiable information when members register
for the forum. We make every effort to protect this information
but may be required by law to hand it over and there is also a security
risk if the database is hacked. We DO NOT sell or give this information
to any third party.
We have
three third party advertisers which set cookies on users' browsers.
Privacy
Statement
This privacy statement covers the site www.bogglesworldesl.com. Because
this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy,
it has agreed to disclose its information practices.
1.      What personally identifiable information
Lanternfish collects.
2.      What personally identifiable information
third parties collect through the Web site.
3.      What organization collects the information.
4.      How Lanternfish ESL
uses the information.
5.      With whom Lanternfish may share
user information.
6.      What choices are available to users
regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
7.      What types of security procedures
are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under
Lanternfish control.
8.      How users can correct any inaccuracies
in the information.
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should
contact Chris Gunn at gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com.
Information Collection and Use
Information Collection:
Lanternfish uses third party ad servers:
,
Google
Adsense. Google Adsense in turn allows other advertising agencies to advertise through them and so by extension they advertise on our site too. This includes Doubleclick.Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a
user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to
your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the
Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page.
(Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of
cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)
These third party ad servers
only collect non-personally identifiable information such as I.P.
addresses and collect aggregate statistics such as page views. For
more details about the information that they collect please view
their privacy statements.
Lanternfish ESL collects both
aggregate information throughout the site and personally indentifiable
information at one point in the site, the discussion forums.
Registration
No information is required to register for this site. However, registration
may be required to use some sections of the member forum. See profile
below:
Information Use
Except for the discussion forums, any information collected on this site by Lanternfish
ESL is of a non-personal
nature.  Boggle'sWorld does not store or keep personal information
on record but does keep aggregate numbers on the number of visitors, method
of arriving at bogglesworldesl.com, location by region, servers, monitor type
and operating systems. To use some sections of the discussion
forum, however, users may be required to provide some personal information
as listed in the profile below. The information collected
in registration will not be used for any purposes other than administering
the board and will never be given or sold to third parties under
any circumstance. However, there is always a security risk from
criminal parties hacking into the MY SQL database that we use.
Profile
Lanternfish ESL does collect profiles of users who wish to register for the
discussion forum. The discussion forum is made from PHPBB2
software. The only information that registrants must supply is a
valid email address. However, the registration sheet does allow
them to provide more information such as job, country, interests,
and other electonic communication channels that they use.  For more information on the
type of information that can be supplied visit the registration
page.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information
about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally
identifiable information while on our site.  We use both session ID
cookies and persistent ID cookies.  For the session ID cookie, once
users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  A persistent
cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended
period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet
browser help file directions.
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).
However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once
we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.
Third Party Advertising
THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT! Third party advertising partners sometimes
conduct surveys or place ads that lead to pages that collect information.
Any personally identifiable information that they collect will actually
be collected off site (i.e. at another website) but since the ads
originated from our site, it may appear that we are collecting information.
These third party
advertisers include Google Adsense and the Hotchalk advertising
network.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files.  This includes
internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider
(ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number
of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement
in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate
use.  IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable
information.
Communications from the Site
NewsletterCurrently, we do not have
a newsletter btu if we do this is the policy we will use: If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information
such as name and email address.  Out of respect for our users privacy
we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the
Choice and Opt-out sections.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related
announcement.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended
for maintenance we might send users an email.  Generally, users may
not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account.
However, these communications are not promotional in nature.  [Users
may opt-out of these communications. Please see our Choice and Opt-out section.]
Customer Service
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services
and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or
phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose
personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief
that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding,
a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers.
This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
These are the instances in which we will share users??personal information:
We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Lanternfish ESL, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to
read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally
identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to
information collected by this Web site.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users??information.
When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information
is protected both online and off-line. Currently, we collect no information
such as personnel ID or credit cards.
If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users
can send an email to gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com <mailto:gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com>
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to
this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate
so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use
it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We will
use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information
was collected.
If, however, we are going to use users??personally identifiable information
in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will
notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we
use their information in this different manner.  However, if users
have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated
their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal
information be used in this new manner.  In addition, if we make any
material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information
already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web
site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice
we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from
us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy,
please contact us at:
Email gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com
Back
to:
